[Music]
Okay, so, as I said earlier,
a helmet is right for safety.
[Music]
This amazing event which is conducted by ICICI
First of all, this ICI Bank,
this school administration, so, thank you to all the parents and
students. Wait for a long time.
First of all, why are our helmets
important? Let's come and
finish it in short. A life should not be lost due to a neck injury.
It should not be an accident and a life loss is not acceptable.
This is not an error with the drivers, it is an
error with the accident money. We have done
our
research and punished all the errors, but it is
useless.
Whoever is punished, it is because there is no use. The
government and the
courts have got involved in this. You should come up with
some scheme,
make some drop, but life should not be
lost for
that.  Penalty Section
Next, do it a lot, do it
no matter how much awareness you have,
but no life should be lost for a trivial reason.
Every year, we have been taking our statistics and
comparing this year with last year, we
have reduced the number of deaths by one fifth in 2023 compared to 2022. Compared to 2022,
2023 is now 24, which should be
much lower. But what is facing us is that the number of vehicles in 2023 is
higher than the number in 2022,
but the infrastructure we have is
the same. So, it is up to
all of us, the road users, to strike this balance and drive without accidents.
Only by using this can we reduce this accident.
You must have seen in this audio the effort taken by this administration and this insurance company to save this life. So, you, students,
your relatives, your friends,
everyone, no one should give us unnecessary
advice. Similarly, no one should disturb our life unnecessarily.
This Terms
and Conditions Road Safety Helmet Awareness is for this
reason. Follow this daily and reduce this life loss. It is
unfair that no life comes and goes carelessly. Take this
opportunity and
all those who drive two wheelers should not drive without a helmet.
Take an incident and follow it daily.
Sir, sir, will you have some camera tape? Okay, okay.
[Music]
Okay, let's do our cheap guest.
Then you
put on a helmet and implement your journey with this helmet.
That's what
our
ready sir, sir, blocking sir,
blocking sir, has come to our side.
[Music] Good
evening to all of you.
Thank you for inviting me to this ICI Lombard free helmet distribution. So, I came to interact with the school children here and brought awareness about the
importance of helmets.
So, ICICI Insurance
Company has given away 3 lakh helmets
all over India.
In 15 cities, they have saved 3 lakh
lives.
If you look at the traffic aspect,  They have saved 15.3 lakh usurers.
So, 9000 helmets
have been given to Sofar in Chennai. So,
why are we starting this from our school zone? We have followed
our rules and
terms and conditions.
We have given this to the generation that comes from this school and will be a clear generation. So,
I request the parents who attended this event and those who are watching this to be road users, to know the terms and conditions and drive on the road accordingly. Thank you, greetings.